# Yano Aki

# Smart contract Engineer

8 years of web application experience & 3 years of smart contract development experience.

I can build **DeFi, Dex, GameFi and NFT** marketplace for you. Innovative ideas, passionate attitudes toward the latest information and technology, and great team spirit. This is how I move forward with you.

drehworld.1994@gmail.com

Setagava City, Tokyo, Japan

# **EDUCATIONS**

2009-2012

**TOKAI UNIVERSITY** 

SCHOOL OF INFORMATION SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

I majored in computational engineering at School Information Science and Technology.

# **SKILLS**



**Solidity** 



Web3



React.js



**Vue.js** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

11/2021-02/2022

# Flan / Lead Blockchain developer

As a job posting site for clients and freelancers, users can proceed with transactions with Crypto Currency. It also makes related data NFT so that they can be resold.

- Built and deployed FLN Token (ERC20 token), Vesting, Airdrop, Staking, Payment and NFT smart contracts on Celo network(EVM network).
- Integrated smart contract to web application using Web3.js
- Deployed own subgraph service for celo network

#### 09/2021-11/2021

## **Ghospers/Lead blockchain developer**

GameFi project with NFT staking, Breeding and Royalties

- Built and deployed GHSP token (BEP20 token), Vesting, Airdrop, GHSP BEP20 token staking, Ghospers NFT staking and Breeding smart contracts on BSC network (EVM network)
- Built NFT mint website
- Integrated smart contract to web application using Web3.js and GraphQL

#### 08/2020-06/2021

## **Convex/Smart contract developer**

As a De-Fi project, Convex allows Curve.fi liquidity providers to earn trading fees and claim boosted CRV without locking CRV themselves. Liquidity providers can receive boosted CRV and liquidity mining rewards with minimal effort.

- Built smart contracts for staking, LP, voting and reward.
- Development of unit test scripts

#### 10/2019-03/2020

# **PEAKDEFI/Smart contract developer**

PEAKDEFI is a crypto ecosystem, that consists of the PEAKDEFI Ethereum App, the decentralized PEAKDEFI platform. Your money be managed by the best experts fully autonomous and proven by the law of blockchain

- Built and deployed smart contracts for staking on Ethereum and BSC network
- Made test scripts

#### 07/2018-06/2019

### **Stixify/Lead developer & CTO**

It is a platform in which users post articles, provide group permission, and support for various vulnerabilities.

- Built web site using Django, Postgresql
- Built apis for Taxii and Stix2

#### 01/2018-05/2018

### **Vulmatch/Major developer**

It is a project that provides customers with the best information about CVE and CPE and allows them to manage their products. I worked on the project, as a lead developer.

 Built web site using Django, React.js, Postgresql, Taxii Api and Stix2 standard

#### 09/2016-10/2017

#### **Mapviewer-3D/Major Developer**

I worked as a major developer in a project to build a web platform that uses the Laravel framework to view 360° images. Database design, creation of functional manuals, coding for Frontend and Backend

- Built web site using Django, Vue.js, Postgresql and Map.js
- Integrated google map api